<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>19 Jan 2023McKesson’s Cross-Cloud Data Journey19 Jan 2023What’s new in Amazon Redshift – 2022, a year in review19 Jan 2023Driving Data, Delivering Value: Data Leaders to Watch in 202318 Jan 2023Leveraging Snowflake to Enable Genomic Analytics at Scale18 Jan 2023Heap Delivers Superior Customer Experiences and Drives Revenue with Snowflake Marketplace18 Jan 2023A dive into redBus’s data platform and how they used Amazon QuickSight to accelerate business insights18 Jan 2023Automate data lineage on Amazon MWAA with OpenLineage17 Jan 2023Enable cross-account sharing with direct IAM principals using AWS Lake Formation Tags17 Jan 2023Build a serverless streaming pipeline with Amazon MSK Serverless, Amazon MSK Connect, and MongoDB Atlas17 Jan 2023How NETSCOUT built a global DDoS awareness platform with Amazon OpenSearch Service17 Jan 2023Build highly available streams with Amazon Kinesis Data Streams17 Jan 2023Build near real-time logistics dashboards using Amazon Redshift and Amazon Managed Grafana for better operational intelligence17 Jan 2023New Snowflake Features Released in December 202217 Jan 2023The Modern Marketing Data Stack and What It Means for Analytics17 Jan 2023Apache Beam 2.</description></item></channel></rss>