<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>23 Nov 2021The Snowflake Holiday Gift Guide for Data Lovers22 Nov 2021Revolution Robotics: A Nonprofit Finds Power in Transformation22 Nov 2021How Robotic Process Automation is Enhancing Corporate Assurance at Adobe22 Nov 2021Provide data reliability in Amazon Redshift at scale using Great Expectations library21 Nov 2021This week in #Scala (Nov 22, 2021)19 Nov 2021Introducing PII data identification and handling using AWS Glue DataBrew19 Nov 2021Attendee guide for the AWS Analytics track at AWS re:Invent 202119 Nov 2021Send personalized email reports with Amazon QuickSight19 Nov 2021How Ethos Powers a Cloud-Native Transformation at Adobe19 Nov 2021Improve Amazon Athena query performance using AWS Glue Data Catalog partition indexes19 Nov 2021Reimagining Replication Agents on AEM as a Cloud Service18 Nov 2021Campaign Budgets at Pinterest18 Nov 2021How Pacific Life Uses the Data Cloud to Enable Data-Driven Decision-Making18 Nov 2021Creating Airbnb’s Page Performance Score18 Nov 2021One Team, One Stream: Disney Streaming unites for its biggest Hackathon yet18 Nov 2021CRISP: Critical Path Analysis for Microservice Architectures18 Nov 2021Accelo uses Amazon QuickSight to accelerate time to value in delivering embedded analytics to professional services businesses18 Nov 2021Design and build a Data Vault model in Amazon Redshift from a transactional database18 Nov 2021Federate Amazon Redshift access with SecureAuth single sign-on18 Nov 2021More Throughput and Faster Execution for Interactive Use Cases: Now in Public Preview17 Nov 2021Create larger SPICE datasets and refresh data faster in Amazon QuickSight with new SPICE features17 Nov 2021Use the Amazon Redshift SQLAlchemy dialect to interact with Amazon Redshift17 Nov 2021Use IP restrictions to control access to Amazon QuickSight17 Nov 2021New Applied ML Prototypes Now Available in Cloudera Machine Learning16 Nov 2021Catalog and analyze Application Load Balancer logs more efficiently with AWS Glue custom classifiers and Amazon Athena16 Nov 2021How GE Aviation built cloud-native data pipelines at enterprise scale using the AWS platform16 Nov 2021MemQ: An efficient, scalable cloud native PubSub system16 Nov 2021Snowday!</description></item></channel></rss>