<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>19 Aug 2021Pinterest’s Analytics as a Platform on Druid (Part 1 of 3)19 Aug 2021Automate Amazon QuickSight user and group management using LDAP data for row-level security19 Aug 2021­­­­­­Introducing AWS Glue 3.0 with optimized Apache Spark 3.1 runtime for faster data integration19 Aug 2021Eats Safety Team On-Call Overview18 Aug 2021Query SAP HANA using Athena Federated Query and join with data in your Amazon S3 data lake18 Aug 2021Make Your First Plugin with Vue JS for Photoshop and Adobe XD18 Aug 2021RAMP-TAO: Layering atomic transactions on Facebook’s online graph store17 Aug 2021A Data-Driven Approach to Telco Success for 5G and Beyond17 Aug 2021Implement row-level security using a complete LDAP hierarchical organization structure in Amazon QuickSight17 Aug 2021Unifying Support Content to Enable More Empathetic and Personalized Customer Support Experiences17 Aug 2021Automating Data Pipelines in CDP with CDE Managed Airflow Service17 Aug 2021Airflow at Societe Generale: Data Orchestration Solution in Banking17 Aug 2021Data Lineage at Slack16 Aug 2021Cloudera DataFlow for the Public Cloud: A technical deep dive16 Aug 2021Apricot subsea cable will boost internet capacity, speeds in the Asia-Pacific region15 Aug 2021This week in #Scala (Aug 16th, 2021)13 Aug 2021Confiar en las métricas en Pinterest13 Aug 2021Efficiently Managing the Supply and Demand on Uber’s Big Data Platform13 Aug 2021Why Modernizing the First Mile of the Data Pipeline Can Accelerate all Analytics12 Aug 2021Standardizing Security Automation Reporting12 Aug 2021Register Now for Snowflake’s Financial Services Data Summit in September12 Aug 2021Improving efficiency and reducing runtime using S3 read optimization11 Aug 2021Object Tagging Is Now Available in Public Preview11 Aug 2021Flowcode Scales Its Data Engineering and Data Science Workloads with Snowflake11 Aug 2021Delivering Threat Detection and Response Without the Limitations11 Aug 2021How We Design Our APIs at Slack11 Aug 2021Cost-Efficient Open Source Big Data Platform at Uber11 Aug 2021Open-sourcing a more precise time appliance10 Aug 2021S&amp;amp;P Global Provides Instant Access to Curated Data10 Aug 2021Power your Kafka Streams application with Amazon MSK and AWS Fargate10 Aug 2021Generating and Viewing Lineage through Apache Ozone10 Aug 2021Task-Oriented Conversational AI in Airbnb Customer Support10 Aug 2021Just-in-Time for Real Life10 Aug 2021How Magellan Rx Management used Amazon Redshift ML to predict drug therapeutic conditions10 Aug 2021What’s New in CDP Private Cloud Base 7.</description></item><item><title>Bear</title><link>https://example.com/bear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/bear/</guid><description>Bear Website: https://bearblog.dev
There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.
Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on any viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.
Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and optimized for search engines.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://example.com/hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo Website: https://gohugo.io
Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description></item></channel></rss>