<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>4 Oct 2021 How Dia &amp;amp; Co Uses Data from Snowflake Data Marketplace to Help Women Get Their Best Clothing Fit4 Oct 2021 Microsoft named a Leader in 2021 Gartner® Magic Quadrant™ for data integration tools3 Oct 2021 This week in #Scala (Oct 4, 2021)1 Oct 2021 Adobe Developers Live: Guide for Document Services30 Sep 2021How Airbnb Tech Fosters a Culture of Learning30 Sep 2021Use Amazon Athena and Amazon QuickSight in a cross-account environment30 Sep 2021Banking on Data, the New Currency of Financial Services30 Sep 2021Snowflake Named “Technology Partner of the Year” by Fivetran30 Sep 2021Simplify your data analysis with Amazon Redshift Query Editor v230 Sep 2021Upgrade to CDP Private Cloud Base – A Step by Step Guide29 Sep 2021Recover in Seconds with Snowflake Client Redirect29 Sep 2021Building Uber’s Fulfillment Platform for Planet-Scale using Google Cloud Spanner29 Sep 2021Amazon QuickSight deployment models for cross-account and cross-Region access to Amazon Redshift and Amazon RDS29 Sep 2021Seven Tips to Creating a Successful Customer Advocacy Program29 Sep 2021Open-sourcing Mariana Trench: Analyzing Android and Java app security in depth29 Sep 2021Paper Clips (Live): Using Adobe PDF Services API Within Web Applications29 Sep 2021Snowflake Partners with and Invests in Anaconda to Bring Enterprise-Grade Open-Source Python Innovation to the Data Cloud29 Sep 2021The Future of Banking: How Can Apache Airflow Help?</description></item></channel></rss>