<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>24 Feb 2023Peek into Adobe Edge Server API24 Feb 2023Build a real-time GDPR-aligned Apache Iceberg data lake24 Feb 2023Meta’s head of AR glasses on the future of AR hardware23 Feb 2023Introducing AWS Glue crawlers using AWS Lake Formation permission management23 Feb 2023Introducing a New Developer Distribution Portal for Listing UXP Plugins in the Creative Cloud…23 Feb 2023Support Organizations Must Recognize the Important Link Between Employee and Customer Experience23 Feb 2023Configure ADFS Identity Federation with Amazon QuickSight23 Feb 2023How Vanguard made their technology platform resilient and efficient by building cross-Region replication for Amazon Kinesis Data Streams23 Feb 2023Control access to Amazon OpenSearch Service Dashboards with attribute-based role mappings23 Feb 2023Ingestion of Healthcare Pricing Transparency Data Files Natively on Snowflake23 Feb 2023Pinterest is now on HTTP/323 Feb 2023Leveraging Data Analytics in the Fight Against Prescription Opioid Abuse22 Feb 2023How Ruparupa gained updated insights with an Amazon S3 data lake, AWS Glue, Apache Hudi, and Amazon QuickSight22 Feb 2023Snowflake’s Phil Kippen Weighs In on Launch of the Telecom Data Cloud21 Feb 2023SQL Streambuilder Data Transformations21 Feb 2023Understand Marketing Channel Effectiveness Using Hidden Markov Model for Conversions in Adobe…21 Feb 2023A hybrid approach in healthcare data warehousing with Amazon Redshift21 Feb 2023Build a data storytelling application with Amazon Redshift Serverless and Toucan21 Feb 2023Meeting Regulatory Reporting and Compliance Standards in the Financial Services Industry with Snowflake21 Feb 2023Startup Spotlight: APIs on Top of Snowflake with Propel21 Feb 2023How SafeGraph built a reliable, efficient, and user-friendly Apache Spark platform with Amazon EMR on Amazon EKS21 Feb 2023How Meta brought AV1 to Reels16 Feb 2023Embrace the Next Industrial Revolution with the Snowflake Data Cloud for Manufacturing16 Feb 2023Tips &amp;amp; Tricks: Using Browser Extensions to Automate Common Workflows16 Feb 2023Bright Data Helps Organizations Access the World’s Largest Data sets with Snowflake16 Feb 2023Prioritizing Home Attributes Based on Guest Interest16 Feb 2023Automate deployment of an Amazon QuickSight analysis connecting to an Amazon Redshift data warehouse with an AWS CloudFormation template16 Feb 2023Inside Meta’s first smart glasses15 Feb 2023Achieve up to 27% better price-performance for Spark workloads with AWS Graviton2 on Amazon EMR Serverless15 Feb 2023Amazon EMR Serverless supports larger worker sizes to run more compute and memory-intensive workloads15 Feb 2023Handle Unpredictable or Ad Hoc Queries with the Query Acceleration Service15 Feb 2023How Strategic Blue uses Amazon QuickSight and AWS Cost and Usage Reports to help their customers save millions15 Feb 2023Are Your Employees a Data Asset or Liability?</description></item></channel></rss>