<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>14 Jun 2021A Collaborative Culture of Experimentation14 Jun 2021This week in #Scala (Jun 14, 2021)11 Jun 2021Predictions Using Advanced Statistical Functions in Adobe Analytics11 Jun 2021Using Machine Learning to De-Blur Photos and Videos; A New College Graduate’s MAX Sneak11 Jun 2021Introduction to AEM as a Cloud Service Asset Upload HTTP API11 Jun 2021La evolución de la búsqueda en Pinterest11 Jun 2021Cómo redujimos el tamaño de la aplicación de Pinterest para iOS en más de un 30% / 50 MB11 Jun 2021El fantástico Fixathon11 Jun 2021Calidad y pruebas de las métricas publicitarias en dispositivos móviles11 Jun 2021Pinterest + ktlint = ❤11 Jun 2021En Pinterest desarrollamos compilaciones para iOS rápidas y confiables11 Jun 2021Administrar videos en Android11 Jun 2021Automate the archival and deletion of sensitive data using Amazon Macie10 Jun 2021DOCOMO empowers business units with self-service knowledge access thanks to agile AWS QuickSight business intelligence10 Jun 2021How to use Apache Spark with CDP Operational Database Experience10 Jun 2021The Evolution of Data Science Workbench10 Jun 2021Level Up Your Customer Experiences with Location-Based Offer Decisioning10 Jun 2021Introducing Adobe Experience Manager’s New Headless Extension for Adobe Commerce PWA Studio9 Jun 2021 Amazon Redshift identity federation with multi-factor authentication9 Jun 2021 The Winner of the Snowflake Startup Challenge Is…9 Jun 2021 Unpacking June 2021 Release: Adobe Document Services9 Jun 2021 Apache Beam 2.</description></item><item><title>Bear</title><link>https://example.com/bear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/bear/</guid><description>Bear Website: https://bearblog.dev
There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.
Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on any viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.
Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and optimized for search engines.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://example.com/hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo Website: https://gohugo.io
Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description></item></channel></rss>