<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>15 Sep 2021How Rapid7 built multi-tenant analytics with Amazon Redshift using near-real-time datasets15 Sep 2021Snowflake Provides the Data Backbone for California’s Digital COVID-19 Vaccine Record15 Sep 2021Generate Documents and Send in Bulk for Signature in Microsoft Power Automate14 Sep 2021How To Get True ROI From Your Account-Based Marketing (ABM)14 Sep 2021Automating Data Protection at Scale, Part 114 Sep 2021Analyze daily trading activity using transaction data from Amazon Redshift in Amazon FinSpace13 Sep 2021New Snowflake Features Released in August 202113 Sep 2021Operating Apache Kafka with Cruise Control13 Sep 2021Superpack: Pushing the limits of compression in Facebook’s mobile apps13 Sep 2021This week in #Scala (Sep 13, 2021)10 Sep 2021Register now for Flink Forward Global, October 26-27, 202110 Sep 2021How Snowflake’s Data Cloud Helps FinServ Customers10 Sep 2021How WhatsApp is enabling end-to-end encrypted backups10 Sep 2021Enabling Multi-User Fine-Grained Access Control for Cloud Storage in CDP9 Sep 2021 Pinterest Home Feed Unified Lightweight Scoring: A Two-tower Approach9 Sep 2021 Taking a Deep Dive into Adobe Experience Manager’s Commerce Integration Framework9 Sep 2021 Embed multi-tenant dashboards in SaaS apps using Amazon QuickSight without provisioning or managing users9 Sep 2021 Improving Third-Party JavaScript Security9 Sep 2021 Migrating Airflow from Amazon EC2 to Kubernetes9 Sep 2021 Embrace the 10-ft.</description></item></channel></rss>