<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>19 Dec 2021This week in #Scala (Dec 20, 2021)17 Dec 2021Cost Reduction in Goku17 Dec 2021Airbnb’s Page Performance Score on Android17 Dec 2021Adobe Developer App Builder Now Available: Extend and Integrate with Adobe Solutions in Minutes17 Dec 2021How The Trade Desk Uses the Data Cloud to Thrive in the Dynamic AdTech World16 Dec 2021Automating Data Protection at Scale, Part 316 Dec 2021Ibotta builds a self-service data lake with AWS Glue16 Dec 2021Cadence Multi-Tenant Task Processing16 Dec 2021Power Loss Siren: Making Meta resilient to power loss events16 Dec 2021What’s new in Amazon Redshift – 2021, a year in review16 Dec 2021How To Overcome Hybrid Cloud Migration Roadblocks16 Dec 2021Snowflake Ventures Invests in Sigma Computing To Ensure Continued Broad Access to the Data Cloud16 Dec 2021Apache Flink Log4j emergency releases15 Dec 2021Introducing new features for Amazon Redshift COPY: Part 115 Dec 2021How Goldman Sachs built persona tagging using Apache Flink on Amazon EMR15 Dec 2021An Interview with Davide Barranca15 Dec 2021Charting the future of our bug bounty program15 Dec 2021Partner Sessions Now Viewable for Snowflake’s Media Data Cloud Summit on January 19, 202215 Dec 2021Stream Apache HBase edits for real-time analytics14 Dec 2021Unify log aggregation and analytics across compute platforms14 Dec 2021Set advanced settings with the Amazon OpenSearch Service Dashboards API14 Dec 2021Powered by Snowflake: How Connected Applications Work14 Dec 2021Use the default IAM role in Amazon Redshift to simplify accessing other AWS services14 Dec 2021Pinterest Analytics como plataforma en Druid (Parte 2 de 3)14 Dec 2021A Simple Kubernetes Admission Webhook14 Dec 2021New Snowflake Features Released In October And November 202113 Dec 2021ConexED uses Amazon QuickSight to empower its institutional partners by unifying and curating powerful insights using engagement data13 Dec 2021View summarized data with Amazon OpenSearch Service Index Transforms13 Dec 2021SLICK: Adopting SLOs for improved reliability13 Dec 2021Hello UAE!</description></item></channel></rss>