<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>19 Sep 2022New Snowflake Features Released in August 202219 Sep 2022Scaling data ingestion for machine learning training at Meta19 Sep 2022SCIM (System for Cross-domain Identity Management)18 Sep 2022This week in #Scala (Sep 19, 2022)16 Sep 2022How ZS created a multi-tenant self-service data orchestration platform using Amazon MWAA15 Sep 2022Using Tabletops and Simulations to Build Better Incident Responders15 Sep 2022Optimize Ama­zon EMR costs for legacy and Spark workloads with managed scaling and node labels15 Sep 2022Adverity is Powered by Snowflake—and Moving into New Markets with Confidence￼15 Sep 2022A Flexible and Efficient Storage System for Diverse Workloads14 Sep 2022How thermal simulation helps optimize Meta’s data centers14 Sep 2022Unique Deep-Dive Insights for a Competitive Industry: TAPP Scales its Data Analytics with Snowflake14 Sep 2022Identify source schema changes using AWS Glue14 Sep 2022Run Apache Spark with Amazon EMR on EKS backed by Amazon FSx for Lustre storage13 Sep 2022Want a Data Renaissance?</description></item></channel></rss>