<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>7 Nov 2021 This week in #Scala (Nov 8, 2021)4 Nov 2021 How Two Interns Are Helping Secure Millions of Lines of Code4 Nov 2021 My Journey to Airbnb — Elizabeth Ponce4 Nov 2021 How 1-800-FLOWERS.COM, Inc. Is Putting Data to Work in the Cloud4 Nov 2021 Go SDK Exits Experimental in Apache Beam 2.33.04 Nov 2021 Rerunning Airflow DAGs3 Nov 2021 Switching from CPUs to GPUs for NYC Taxi Fare Predictions with NVIDIA RAPIDS3 Nov 2021 Introducing Amazon S3 shuffle in AWS Glue3 Nov 2021 Integrate AWS Glue DataBrew and Amazon PinPoint to launch marketing campaigns3 Nov 2021 Flink Backward - The Apache Flink Retrospective2 Nov 2021 TrueBlue uses Amazon QuickSight to deliver more accurate pricing and grow business2 Nov 2021 Query hierarchical data models within Amazon Redshift2 Nov 2021 Key foundations for protecting your data with Azure confidential computing2 Nov 2021 Transform your business with Microsoft's unrivaled end-to-end data platform1 Nov 2021 Four Rules to Make Partners Your Marketing Differentiator1 Nov 2021 This week in #Scala (Nov 1, 2021)29 Oct 2021Creating a Bootstrap Carousel from Core Components29 Oct 2021Now Available: Updated guidance on the Data Analytics Lens for AWS Well-Architected Framework29 Oct 2021Cybersecurity Awareness Month: Learn about the job zero of securing your data using Amazon Redshift29 Oct 2021High Availability (Multi-AZ) for CDP Operational Database28 Oct 2021Adobe Analytics Labs: Expediting Machine Learning Innovation28 Oct 2021React &amp;amp; RxJS: Pushing state down28 Oct 2021Data Engineers of Netflix — Interview with Pallavi Phadnis28 Oct 2021Democratizing the Data Stack—Airflow for Business Workflows27 Oct 2021Snowflake Announces Support for Google Cloud Private Service Connect27 Oct 2021Building a Security Training Testbed for Azure26 Oct 2021Copy large datasets from Google Cloud Storage to Amazon S3 using Amazon EMR26 Oct 2021Kangaroo: A new flash cache optimized for tiny objects26 Oct 2021Snowflake Advanced Certifications: Level Up to SnowPro Advanced and Show Off Your Snowflake Expertise26 Oct 2021Automate building an integrated analytics solution with AWS Analytics Automation Toolkit26 Oct 2021Adobe MAX 2021: Your Guide to Document Cloud Sessions26 Oct 2021Accelerate large-scale data migration validation using PyDeequ26 Oct 2021Meet Ottr: A Serverless Public Key Infrastructure Framework26 Oct 2021The Ultimate Map to finding Halloween candy surplus26 Oct 2021Machine Learning Pipelines: Everything You Need to Know26 Oct 2021Accelerating healthcare AI innovation with Zero Trust technology26 Oct 2021Sort-Based Blocking Shuffle Implementation in Flink - Part Two26 Oct 2021Sort-Based Blocking Shuffle Implementation in Flink - Part One25 Oct 2021New Features in Cloudera Streams Messaging Public Cloud 7.</description></item></channel></rss>