<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>3 Aug 2021 How Cisco Optimized Performance on Snowflake to Reduce Costs 15%: Part 23 Aug 2021 Fighting Spam using Clustering and Automated Rule Creation3 Aug 2021 Secure connectivity patterns to access Amazon MSK across AWS Regions3 Aug 2021 Effective data lakes using AWS Lake Formation, Part 5: Securing data lakes with row-level access control3 Aug 2021 Creating Hulu VR3 Aug 2021 Voidbox-Docker on YARN3 Aug 2021 Hulu Moves Data Centers to 100 Percent Renewable Energy Facility3 Aug 2021 Introducing the Hulu Technical Landscape3 Aug 2021 Uber’s Finance Computation Platform2 Aug 2021 Major Brands Democratize Data with Snowpark Accelerated2 Aug 2021 Dentsu Tracking Partners with Snowflake for Data Intelligence Services for the World’s Largest Regulated Tracking and Tracing Platform2 Aug 2021 Connect to Snowflake with JDBC2 Aug 2021 Connect to Snowflake with JDBC2 Aug 2021 Benchmark the performance of the new Auto WLM with adaptive concurrency in Amazon Redshift2 Aug 2021 How GE Healthcare modernized their data platform using a Lake House Architecture2 Aug 2021 Replace and Boost your Apache Storm Topologies with Apache NiFi Flows2 Aug 2021 Finding Your Feet with Project Firefly1 Aug 2021 This week in #Scala (Aug 2nd, 2021)31 Jul 2021Executing Notebooks with Airflow30 Jul 2021Chipotle Leverages Snowflake to Inform Decision-Making During the Pandemic30 Jul 2021Rework Your Angular Development Workflow30 Jul 2021Snowflake’s Retail and CPG Data Analytics Forum: Now Available on Demand29 Jul 2021Use the Data Cloud to (finally) Demystify Data Governance29 Jul 2021Embed Amazon AppFlow in your applications using APIs29 Jul 2021Delivering Company-wide Security through Cross-collaboration29 Jul 2021Visualize data using Apache Spark running on Amazon EMR with Amazon QuickSight29 Jul 2021Pinot Real-Time Ingestion with Cloud Segment Storage29 Jul 2021A linear programming approach for optimizing features in ML models29 Jul 2021What Is Data Orchestration and Why Is It Essential for Business29 Jul 2021A Window of Opportunity to the Data Cloud28 Jul 2021Unleash Advanced Geospatial Analytics in Snowflake28 Jul 2021Build a centralized granular access control to manage assets and data access in Amazon QuickSight28 Jul 2021Scaling a Company to IPO and Beyond28 Jul 2021Email Classification27 Jul 2021Calculated fields, level-aware aggregations, and evaluation order in Amazon QuickSight27 Jul 2021How PepsiCo Gains Actionable Insights Using the Data Cloud27 Jul 2021Modern Data Infrastructure for Freedom to Explore27 Jul 2021Uber’s Fulfillment Platform: Ground-up Re-architecture to Accelerate Uber’s Go/Get Strategy27 Jul 2021Using Sentiment Score to Assess Customer Service Quality27 Jul 2021Get a Document Generated and E-Signed Using a Chatbot27 Jul 2021Airflow Summit 2021 Highlights 26 Jul 2021Access Amazon Location Service from Amazon Redshift26 Jul 2021This week in #Scala (Jul 26, 2021)23 Jul 2021Building the Infrastructure of the New Economy: Meet Snowflake’s New Head of Canada, Bilal Khan23 Jul 2021AEM as a Cloud Service — Dispatcher Converter Tool22 Jul 2021Synchronize and control your Amazon Redshift clusters maintenance windows22 Jul 2021Unpacking July 2021 Release: Adobe Document Services22 Jul 2021Accelerate your data warehouse migration to Amazon Redshift – Part 222 Jul 2021Establish private connectivity between Amazon QuickSight and Snowflake using AWS PrivateLink22 Jul 2021Containerizing Apache Hadoop Infrastructure at Uber22 Jul 2021Migrating Facebook to MySQL 8.</description></item><item><title>Bear</title><link>https://example.com/bear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/bear/</guid><description>Bear Website: https://bearblog.dev
There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.
Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on any viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.
Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and optimized for search engines.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://example.com/hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo Website: https://gohugo.io
Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description></item></channel></rss>