<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>23 Nov 2022Create small multiples in Amazon QuickSight23 Nov 2022Add text boxes to your Amazon QuickSight analysis23 Nov 2022New line chart customization options in Amazon QuickSight23 Nov 2022Using PDF Embed API with SharePoint23 Nov 2022Implement row-level access control in a multi-tenant environment with Amazon Redshift23 Nov 2022How AI Text Generation Models Are Reshaping Customer Support at Airbnb23 Nov 2022Alerts and Observability for Pipeline Monitoring and Cost Management22 Nov 2022Be The Match Improves Likelihood of Life-Saving Patient Outcomes by Partnering with Snowflake and DAS4222 Nov 2022Hybrid Personalization in the Adobe Experience Platform Web SDK22 Nov 2022The Pandemic was Telehealth’s Baptism by Fire: Here Are its Impacts22 Nov 2022Build your Apache Hudi data lake on AWS using Amazon EMR – Part 122 Nov 2022How Etleap and Amazon Redshift Serverless optimize costs for ETL22 Nov 2022Retrofitting null-safety onto Java at Meta21 Nov 2022Govern and manage permissions of Amazon QuickSight assets with the new centralized asset management console21 Nov 2022Design a Tracking cum Reporting Dashboard for SaltStack21 Nov 2022Using Sling Feature Flags to Manage Continuous Releases21 Nov 2022Amazon Alexa Audio migrates business intelligence to Amazon QuickSight for faster performance21 Nov 2022Automate your Amazon QuickSight deployment with the new API-based account creation and deletion21 Nov 2022How GoDaddy built a data mesh to decentralize data ownership using AWS Lake Formation21 Nov 2022Get started with data integration from Amazon S3 to Amazon Redshift using AWS Glue interactive sessions21 Nov 2022Data Vault Techniques on Snowflake: Virtual Warehouses and Charge Back21 Nov 20223 Ways Technology Can Build Data Economy Leadership—or Hold You Back21 Nov 2022Building Airbnb Categories with ML and Human-in-the-Loop21 Nov 2022PTP: Timing accuracy and precision for the future of computing21 Nov 2022How Precision Time Protocol is being deployed at Meta20 Nov 2022This week in #Scala (Nov 21, 2022)19 Nov 2022Introducing ACK controller for Amazon EMR on EKS18 Nov 2022Announcing AWS Glue crawler support for Snowflake18 Nov 2022BUILD 2022: Building the Next Generation of Applications18 Nov 2022How ENGIE automates the deployment of Amazon Athena data sources on Microsoft Power BI18 Nov 2022Enriching Streams with Hive tables via Flink SQL17 Nov 2022Announcing the latest version of the AWS Well-Architected Data Analytics Lens17 Nov 2022Accessing Photoshop Neural Filters Programmatically17 Nov 2022Share and publish your Snowflake data to AWS Data Exchange using Amazon Redshift data sharing17 Nov 2022Use Karpenter to speed up Amazon EMR on EKS autoscaling17 Nov 2022Apache Beam 2.</description></item></channel></rss>