<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>28 Jan 2022Monthly Office Hours with the Creative Cloud Platform and Ecosystem Team28 Jan 2022Integrating AI Computer Vision with Your PDF Documents28 Jan 2022Data and Customer Privacy: What Companies Need to Do28 Jan 2022Snowflake Gets Pragmatic in Poland27 Jan 2022Add comparative and cumulative date/time calculations in Amazon QuickSight27 Jan 2022Snowpark Is Now Generally Available26 Jan 2022Guía del equipo de Ingeniería de Pinterest para entrevistas técnicas26 Jan 2022Cómo es el proceso de entrevistas de ingeniería en Pinterest25 Jan 2022Validate streaming data over Amazon MSK using schemas in cross-account AWS Glue Schema Registry25 Jan 2022Make the Leap to AI Driven Data Applications25 Jan 2022Cost Efficiency @ Scale in Big Data File Format25 Jan 2022Snowflake’s Media Data Cloud Summit: Now Available on Demand!</description></item></channel></rss>