<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>1 Jul 2021 Data preparation using Amazon Redshift with AWS Glue DataBrew1 Jul 2021 Successfully Measuring Advertising Performance On Demand1 Jul 2021 The Great BBQ Breakdown1 Jul 2021 Improving data processing efficiency using partial deserialization of Thrift1 Jul 2021 Adobe Experience Manager GraphQL API: Easy, Efficient Content Delivery30 Jun 2021Novartis Leverages the Data Cloud to Secure and Unify Fragmented Data30 Jun 2021A New Ethics of AI30 Jun 2021Build a real-time streaming analytics pipeline with the AWS CDK30 Jun 2021Continuous Integration and Deployment for Machine Learning Online Serving and Models29 Jun 2021A Deep Dive into Airbnb’s Server-Driven UI System29 Jun 2021Organizing for Accelerating Insights to Impact: The 3 C’s of Being Insights-Driven29 Jun 2021How Starschema Uses Snowflake Data Marketplace to Share a Trusted COVID-19 Data Set29 Jun 2021Multi-Lingual Personalization at Scale with Experience Fragments (AEM and Target)29 Jun 2021This week in #Scala (Jun 28, 2021)28 Jun 2021Data Visualization28 Jun 2021XD Plugins Are Moving to the Marketplace in Creative Cloud Desktop28 Jun 2021Effective data lakes using AWS Lake Formation, Part 4: Implementing cell-level and row-level security28 Jun 2021ECID Migration with AEP Web SDK28 Jun 2021Asicmon: A platform agnostic observability system for AI accelerators28 Jun 2021Driving towards an open internet ecosystem to help tackle the digital divide25 Jun 2021Work with semistructured data using Amazon Redshift SUPER25 Jun 2021Adding Hooks to the Photoshop UXP React Plugin Samples25 Jun 2021Migrate Hive data from CDH to CDP public cloud24 Jun 2021Prisma Health Streamlines Healthcare Costs with Data-Driven Insights that Enhance Preventative Care24 Jun 2021Deploying applications on CDP Operational Database (COD)24 Jun 2021Setting Up Snowflake Secondary Roles with Tableau24 Jun 2021Increase Amazon Elasticsearch Service performance by upgrading to Graviton223 Jun 2021Integrating Salesforce Data with Snowflake Using Tableau CRM Sync Out23 Jun 2021The Rocket Behind Snowflake’s Rocketship23 Jun 2021Join Microsoft at ISC 2021 and drive innovations with Azure high-performance computing23 Jun 2021Global Retailer Standardizing On Airflow for Data-Driven Decisions22 Jun 2021Are You and Your Plugin Ready for Apple Silicon?</description></item><item><title>Bear</title><link>https://example.com/bear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/bear/</guid><description>Bear Website: https://bearblog.dev
There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.
Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on any viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.
Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and optimized for search engines.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://example.com/hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo Website: https://gohugo.io
Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description></item></channel></rss>