<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>12 Oct 2021Why Collecting the Right Metadata is Crucial for Scaling a Security Program12 Oct 2021Migrating Kafka transparently between Zookeeper clusters12 Oct 2021Do Your UX Designs Support Content Authors?12 Oct 2021Continuous monitoring with Sumo Logic using Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose HTTP endpoints12 Oct 2021Build and orchestrate ETL pipelines using Amazon Athena and AWS Step Functions12 Oct 2021What is new in Cloudera Streaming Analytics 1.5?12 Oct 2021Key Pricing Considerations for Building and Delivering SaaS Solutions12 Oct 2021Everything You Need to Know about Apache Airflow 2.</description></item></channel></rss>