<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>19 Dec 2022Improve Jest Runner Performance19 Dec 2022Run fault tolerant and cost-optimized Spark clusters using Amazon EMR on EKS and Amazon EC2 Spot Instances19 Dec 2022Top analytics announcements of AWS re:Invent 202219 Dec 2022Monitor AWS workloads without a single line of code with Logz.io and Kinesis Firehose19 Dec 2022Introducing native Delta Lake table support with AWS Glue crawlers19 Dec 2022How DTCC Uses the Data Cloud to Meet the Needs of Internal and External Customers19 Dec 2022New Snowflake Features Released in October and November 202216 Dec 2022Getting started with AWS Glue Data Quality for ETL Pipelines16 Dec 2022Getting started with AWS Glue Data Quality from the AWS Glue Data Catalog16 Dec 2022SafeGraph Accelerates Customer Time to Value by 60% with Snowflake Marketplace16 Dec 2022AWS Marketplace Seller Insights team uses Amazon QuickSight Embedded to empower sellers with actionable business insights16 Dec 2022One Year of Creative Cloud Plugin Showcases16 Dec 2022Amazon EMR Serverless cost estimator15 Dec 2022Analyze real-time streaming data in Amazon MSK with Amazon Athena15 Dec 2022LaunchDarkly’s journey from ingesting 1 TB to 100 TB per day with Amazon Kinesis Data Streams15 Dec 2022Startup Spotlight: Q&amp;amp;A with Flipside15 Dec 2022How River Island Sustainably Navigates Uncertainty Through the Golden Quarter With Snowflake14 Dec 2022Migrate Google BigQuery to Amazon Redshift using AWS Schema Conversion tool (SCT)14 Dec 2022Create, Train and Deploy Multi Layer Perceptron (MLP) models using Amazon Redshift ML14 Dec 2022Secure your database credentials with AWS Secrets Manager and encrypt data with AWS KMS in Amazon QuickSight14 Dec 2022How Financial Services Drive Efficient Insurance Underwriting with the Snowflake Data Cloud14 Dec 2022Integrate Adobe Experience Manager Assets Essentials and Adobe Workfront to Easily Manage Your…14 Dec 2022Apache Flink Kubernetes Operator 1.</description></item></channel></rss>