<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>6 Oct 2021 WeatherBug reduced ETL latency to 30 times faster using Amazon Redshift Spectrum6 Oct 2021 Create Probabilistic Cross-Device Household Graphs Using CTV Devices Data in Adobe Primetime6 Oct 2021 Automate your Amazon Redshift performance tuning with automatic table optimization6 Oct 2021 BUILD 2021: The Future of Development on Snowflake5 Oct 2021 Announcing Snowflake Startup Challenge 2022 with Prizes Totaling Up to $1M5 Oct 2021 Query your Amazon MSK topics interactively using Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics Studio5 Oct 2021 Authorize SparkSQL data manipulation on Amazon EMR using Apache Ranger5 Oct 2021 Designing for Productivity in a Large-Scale iOS Application5 Oct 2021 More details about the October 4 outage5 Oct 2021 An Introduction to Ranger RMS5 Oct 2021 An HBase &amp;amp; HDFS Short-Circuit Read Odyssey5 Oct 2021 Big Data Architecture: Core Components, Use Cases and Limitations5 Oct 2021 Struggling to Manage your Multi-Tenant Environments?</description></item></channel></rss>