<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>10 May 2021New Snowflake Features Released In April 202110 May 2021Shallow Mirror10 May 2021Manage and process your big data workflows with Amazon MWAA and Amazon EMR on Amazon EKS10 May 2021Documentation Testing &amp;amp; Hashing with Javascript (Ferrum.js 1.9)10 May 2021Building the Hulu Experience in the Living Room10 May 2021Building Hulu’s Living Room Experience with Amazon Alexa10 May 2021How the Data Cloud Helps Marketers Achieve Personalization at Scale10 May 2021Most of computing’s carbon emissions are coming from manufacturing and infrastructure10 May 2021cdpcurl: Low-Level CDP API Access9 May 2021 This week in #Scala (May 10, 2021)7 May 2021 Snowflake Data Marketplace Winners Announced7 May 2021 Steps to Merge XML Data in Existing PDF Forms7 May 2021 Watch Session Highlights from Snowflake’s Healthcare and Life Sciences Forum6 May 2021 Securing Apache Kafka is easy and familiar with IAM Access Control for Amazon MSK6 May 2021 Merging Data with Documents Using Adobe Document Generation API6 May 2021 Enabling a “Secure by Requirement” Approach6 May 2021 Optimal Feature Discovery: Better, Leaner Machine Learning Models Through Information Theory6 May 2021 Part 1: Run Adobe Target NodeJS SDK for Experimentation and Personalization on Edge Platforms…6 May 2021 Scaling Flink automatically with Reactive Mode5 May 2021 How JPMorgan Chase built a data mesh architecture to drive significant value to enhance their enterprise data platform5 May 2021 Use HyperLogLog for trend analysis with Amazon Redshift5 May 2021 Data’s Evolution in the Cloud: Data Helps Engage Customers in Media and Entertainment5 May 2021 Spark on Kubernetes – Gang Scheduling with YuniKorn5 May 2021 Validate your Apache Airflow Skills with the Astronomer Certification4 May 2021 How Anthem Achieves Holistic Healthcare Using Snowflake’s Data Cloud4 May 2021 Effective data lakes using AWS Lake Formation, Part 3: Using ACID transactions on governed tables4 May 2021 Streaming Market Data with Flink SQL Part I: Streaming VWAP4 May 2021 How does Airbnb track and measure growth marketing?</description></item><item><title>Bear</title><link>https://example.com/bear/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/bear/</guid><description>Bear Website: https://bearblog.dev
There is a website obesity crisis. Bloated websites are full of scripts, ads, and trackers slowing your readers down every time they try to read your well-crafted content.
Bear is all you need to build a fantastic and optimized site or blog. It works perfectly on any viewing device. All you need to focus on is writing good content.
Bear makes it simple to publish content online and grow an audience while keeping pages tiny, fast, and optimized for search engines.</description></item><item><title>Hugo</title><link>https://example.com/hugo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/hugo/</guid><description>Hugo Website: https://gohugo.io
Written in Go, Hugo is an open-source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML, and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files, and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification, and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:</description></item></channel></rss>