<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>17 Nov 2022Announcing the latest version of the AWS Well-Architected Data Analytics Lens17 Nov 2022Accessing Photoshop Neural Filters Programmatically17 Nov 2022Share and publish your Snowflake data to AWS Data Exchange using Amazon Redshift data sharing17 Nov 2022Use Karpenter to speed up Amazon EMR on EKS autoscaling17 Nov 2022Snowflake for Marketing with Flywheel16 Nov 2022Fulfillment by Amazon uses Amazon QuickSight to deliver key reporting insights to Amazon Marketplace sellers16 Nov 2022What’s new with AWS Glue at AWS re:Invent 202216 Nov 2022Move faster, wait less: Improving code review time at Meta16 Nov 2022How Retailers Deliver Seamless Omnichannel Experiences with the Snowflake Retail Data Cloud15 Nov 2022Your guide to streaming data &amp;amp; real-time analytics at re:Invent 202215 Nov 2022Adobe Experience Platform Mobile SDK for Apple watchOS15 Nov 2022Slow Into the Turn, Accelerate Out: Implement Cost Governance To Accelerate Cloud Adoption15 Nov 2022NYSE Joins the 2023 Snowflake Startup Challenge15 Nov 2022Use an event-driven architecture to build a data mesh on AWS15 Nov 2022Sapling: Source control that’s user-friendly and scalable15 Nov 2022Unlocking HBase on S3 With the New Store File Tracking Feature15 Nov 2022Flexible Daily Budgeting at Pinterest14 Nov 2022Snowflake Recertifications: Navigating Snowflake’s Maintenance Paths14 Nov 2022Aramisauto Boosts its Customer Experience Through High-Performance Data Processing and Analysis at Scale with Snowflake14 Nov 2022Snowflake’s Commitment to Continuously Improve Economics for Our Customers14 Nov 2022Build an optimized self-service interactive analytics platform with Amazon EMR Studio14 Nov 2022This week in #Scala (Nov 14, 2022)11 Nov 2022Builders Unite: 5 Reasons to Attend BUILD 2022 – The Data Cloud Dev Summit10 Nov 2022How Hudl built a cost-optimized AWS Glue pipeline with Apache Hudi datasets10 Nov 2022Transforming a Huge Monolith into Micro Frontends10 Nov 2022How a Data Cloud Unlocks AI/ML Innovation at Scale10 Nov 2022How SOCAR built a streaming data pipeline to process IoT data for real-time analytics and control9 Nov 2022 Multiple Performant Operations with the New Adobe Document Services REST APIs9 Nov 2022 Learn more about Apache Flink and Amazon Kinesis Data Analytics with three new videos9 Nov 2022 How Retailers Improve Personalized Marketing with the Snowflake Retail Data Cloud9 Nov 2022 Tulip: Schematizing Meta’s data platform9 Nov 2022 Enrich VPC Flow Logs with resource tags and deliver data to Amazon S3 using Amazon Kinesis Data Firehose9 Nov 2022 How Kyligence Cloud uses Amazon EMR Serverless to simplify OLAP9 Nov 2022 Keep Going Global: New Cross-Cloud Capabilities with Snowgrid9 Nov 2022 New Resources Available for Beam ML8 Nov 2022 Why Data Should Be the Foundation of Every Retailer’s Sustainability Strategy8 Nov 2022 Ozone Write Pipeline V2 with Ratis Streaming8 Nov 2022 A Faster, More Efficient Snowflake Takes the Stage at Snowday8 Nov 2022 Dynamic Tables: Delivering Declarative Streaming Data Pipelines with Snowflake8 Nov 2022 Field-level security in Amazon OpenSearch Service8 Nov 2022 Reduce cost and improve query performance with Amazon Athena Query Result Reuse7 Nov 2022 Developers Rejoice!</description></item></channel></rss>