<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.com/yuin/goldmark https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>10 Mar 2023Effortless Data Ingestion to Adobe Experience Platform with Data Landing Zone Connector10 Mar 2023Adobe PDF Embed API Now Available as a WordPress Plugin10 Mar 2023Build a serverless transactional data lake with Apache Iceberg, Amazon EMR Serverless, and Amazon Athena10 Mar 2023Apache Beam 2.46.09 Mar 2023 Enhance your analytics embedding experience with the new Amazon QuickSight JavaScript SDK9 Mar 2023 Simplify data loading into Type 2 slowly changing dimensions in Amazon Redshift9 Mar 2023 Wand Powers AI Analytics at Scale Using Snowflake’s Data Cloud9 Mar 2023 Introducing Velox: An open source unified execution engine8 Mar 2023 Mitigating Financial Crime Incidents in the Financial Services Sector8 Mar 2023 Build an end-to-end change data capture with Amazon MSK Connect and AWS Glue Schema Registry7 Mar 2023 How Financial Services Companies Optimize Quantitative Research with the Snowflake Data Cloud 7 Mar 2023 How gaming companies can use Amazon Redshift Serverless to build scalable analytical applications faster and easier7 Mar 2023 Improve productivity by using keyboard shortcuts in Amazon Athena query editor7 Mar 2023 Data Sharing Is Caring: Driving Sustainability with Data7 Mar 2023 Using Machine Learning to Help Detect Sensitive Information6 Mar 2023 Hosting Multiple Tenants on AEM6 Mar 2023 How Retailers Can Improve Supply Chain Efficiency and Collaboration with Channel Partners3 Mar 2023 Build incremental data pipelines to load transactional data changes using AWS DMS, Delta 2.</description></item></channel></rss>