<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>5 Jan 2022 Set up cross-account audit logging for your Amazon Redshift cluster5 Jan 2022 Snowflake Announces New Integration With Microsoft Azure Purview4 Jan 2022 Why Snowflake Was My Next Strategic Move After Google4 Jan 2022 Federate access to Amazon Redshift using the JDBC browser plugin for Single Sign-on authentication with Microsoft Azure Active Directory4 Jan 2022 Optimize your analytical workloads using the automatic query rewrite feature of Amazon Redshift materialized views4 Jan 2022 Disney Streaming Embraces 3 Key Tenets of Experimentation4 Jan 2022 How We Improved Scheduler Performance for Large-scale Jobs - Part Two4 Jan 2022 How We Improved Scheduler Performance for Large-scale Jobs - Part One3 Jan 2022 This week in #Scala (Jan 3, 2022)30 Dec 2021SearchSage: aprendizaje de las representaciones de consultas de búsqueda en Pinterest30 Dec 2021The top Pinterest Engineering blog posts from 202129 Dec 2021How Belcorp decreased cost and improved reliability in its big data processing framework using Amazon EMR managed scaling29 Dec 2021Apache Beam 2.</description></item></channel></rss>