<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Datalog.so</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Datalog.so</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2020, Jane Doe.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Markdown Syntax Guide</title><link>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/markdown-syntax-guide/</guid><description>&lt;p>For a quick cheatsheet, check out &lt;a href="https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide">https://simplemde.com/markdown-guide&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;hr>
&lt;p>This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Time traveling in data lakes</title><link>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/time-traveling-in-data-lakes/</guid><description>Some text about data lakes idk</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://example.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/about/</guid><description>Written in Go, Hugo is an open source static site generator available under the Apache Licence 2.0. Hugo supports TOML, YAML and JSON data file types, Markdown and HTML content files and uses shortcodes to add rich content. Other notable features are taxonomies, multilingual mode, image processing, custom output formats, HTML/CSS/JS minification and support for Sass SCSS workflows.
Hugo makes use of a variety of open source projects including:
https://github.</description></item><item><title>Newsletter</title><link>https://example.com/newsletter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://example.com/newsletter/</guid><description>8 Sep 2021 Federated authentication to Amazon Redshift using AWS Single Sign-On8 Sep 2021 Implement anti-money laundering solutions on AWS8 Sep 2021 Introducing the Disney+ Application Development Kit (ADK)8 Sep 2021 Supporting Transformation with an Integrated Data Platform. Three Common Questions Answered.7 Sep 2021 Snowflake Data Cloud and Snowflake Data Marketplace Inform Game Dev, Delivers Business Insights at 2K Games7 Sep 2021 How to attribute Amazon Redshift costs to your end-users7 Sep 2021 Pinterest’s Analytics as a Platform on Druid (Part 3 of 3)7 Sep 2021 How CRED Built 90+ DAGs in 6 months with Astronomer7 Sep 2021 Behind the Scenes of Slack’s Acquisition Announcement7 Sep 2021 Implementing a custom source connector for Table API and SQL - Part Two 7 Sep 2021 Implementing a Custom Source Connector for Table API and SQL - Part One 5 Sep 2021 This week in #Scala (Sep 6th, 2021)3 Sep 2021 Datafacts — A Project Firefly Application for Adobe Experience Platform3 Sep 2021 How to Build an ETL Process?</description></item></channel></rss>